LIVE FROM HAWAII.
Gabriel Iglesias: Aloha Fluffy is a comedy, tv movie
film directed by Manny Rodriguez.
Internationally acclaimed comedian, Gabriel Iglesias, returns to Comedy Central with
his latest stand-up special taped at Honolulu’s Hawaii Theatre Center.
Watch as Fluffy brings the house down yet again in this complete special with his
unique and animated show that has made him popular among fans of all ages.
Aloha Fluffy is sure to be a comedy classic, making this
extended and uncensored special a must-own.
Himself, played by Gabriel Iglesias.
Self, played by Martin Moreno.
Self, played by G Reilly.
Gabriel Jesús Iglesias (born July 15, 1976), nicknamed Fluffy,
is an American stand-up comedian and actor.
He has produced a number of stand-up specials for television outlets such
as Comedy Central and Netflix, including I'm Not Fat...
I'm Fluffy, and Hot and Fluffy.
As an actor, he has appeared in numerous live-action and animated TV
shows and films, including starring in the sitcom Mr.
Iglesias on Netflix, playing Tobias in the 2012 movie Magic Mike and its 2015 sequel,
and providing the voice of Speedy Gonzales in Space Jam: A New Legacy.
He was also the host of the shows Stand Up Revolution on Comedy
Central and Fluffy's Food Adventures on Fuse.
In 2018, Iglesias was one of the top 10 highest paid comedians in the world.
The tone is lighthearted.